<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Inspiration</string>

    <string name="line">____________________________________________________________________</string>
    <string name="name">THIS APP CONTAINS AN INSPIRATIONAL MESSAGES THAT WILL HELP YOU GROW SPIRITUALLY</string>

    <string name="victory_through_jesus">VICTORY THROUGH JESUS</string>
    <string name="main_victory_throgh_jesus">\tBecause man fallen could not overcome Satan with his human strength,
        Christ came from the royal courts of heaven to help him with His human and divine strength combined.\n\n

Christ knew that Adam in Eden with his superior advantages might have withstood the temptations of Satan and conquered him.\n\n

He also knew that it was not possible for man out of Eden, separated from the light and love of God since the fall,
        to resist the temptations of Satan in his own strength.\n\n

In order to bring hope to man, and save him from complete ruin, He humbled Himself to take man\'s nature,
        that with His divine power combined with the human He might reach man where he is.\n\n

He obtained for the fallen sons and daughters of Adam that strength which it is impossible for them to gain for themselves, that in His name they might overcome the temptations of Satan.\n\n

The exalted Son of God in assuming humanity draws Himself near to man by standing as the sinner\'s substitute.\n\n

He identifies Himself with the sufferings and afflictions of men. He was tempted in all points as man is tempted, that He might know how to succor those who should be tempted. Christ overcame on the sinner\'s behalf.\n\n

Jacob in the night vision saw earth connected with heaven by a ladder reaching to the throne of God.\n\n

He saw the angels of God, clothed with garments of heavenly brightness, passing down from heaven and up to heaven upon this shining ladder.\n\n

The bottom of this ladder rested upon the earth, while the top of it reached to the highest heavens and rested upon the throne of Jehovahn\n\n

The brightness from the throne of God beamed down upon this ladder and reflected a light of inexpressible glory upon the earth.\n\n

This ladder represented Christ, who had opened the communication between earth and heaven.\n\n

In Christ\'s humiliation He descended to the very depths of human woe in sympathy and pity for fallen man, which was represented to Jacob by one end of the ladder resting upon the earth, while the top of the ladder, reaching unto heaven, represents the divine power of Christ grasping the Infinite and thus linking earth to heaven and finite man to the infinite God.\n\n

Through Christ the communication is opened between God and man. Angels may pass to and fro from heaven to earth with messages of love to fallen man, and to minister unto those who shall be heirs of salvation. It is through Christ alone that the heavenly messengers minister to men.\n\n

Adam and Eve in Eden were placed under most favorable circumstances. It was their privilege to hold communion with God and angels.\n\n

They were without the condemnation of sin. The light of God and angels was with them and around about them.\n\n

The Author of their existence was their teacher. But they fell beneath the power and temptations of the artful foe.\n\n

Four thousand years had Satan been at work against the government of God, and he had obtained strength and experience from determined practice.\n\n

Fallen men had not the advantages of Adam in Eden. They had been separating from God for four thousand years.\n\n

The wisdom to understand, and power to resist, the temptations of Satan had become less and less, until Satan seemed to reign triumphant in the earth.\n\n

Appetite and passion, the love of the world, and presumptuous sins were the great branches of evil out of which every species of crime, violence, and corruption grew.\n\n
Satan was defeated in his object to overcome Christ upon the point of appetite. And here in the wilderness Christ achieved a victory in behalf of the race upon the point of appetite, making it possible for man, in all future time in His name to overcome the strength of appetite on his own behalf.</string>


    <string name="positve_thinking">positive Thinking</string>
    <string name="main_positive_thinking">\nPOSITIVE THINKING\n\n

        The power of positive thinking is another mind power technique to help you get the things you wants in life.\n
    This will also help enhance your health and even your spiritual and emotional growth.\n\n\n

    Remember that the impact of positive thinking will change your life for the better.\n
    This means that you need to erase the negative aspects of your mind. Your mind should stay focused and think of the positive things that are already happening in tour life.\n\n\n
    However, how are you able to erase the negative thought that runs through your mind? Well the first thing you need to do is;\n\n
       1. To search for the main cause of positivity in your mind. Once you have \"located\" it, think deeply and look within you. Once you have found the answers to these negative thought, Vanish it by empowering your mind with the positive thinking.With this you are able to eliminate the negative images in your mind and you can move forward towards achieving your goals in the positive way.\n\n\n
        To further enhance your positive thinking, consider these steps and to be on the road to success in attaining your positive goes in life.\n\n\n</string>


    <string name="the_three_fold_nature_of_man">\tTHE THREE FOLD NATURE OF MAN</string>
    <string name="main_he_three_fold_nature_of_man" translatable="false">The study of man\'s three-fold 
        nature—the spirit, soul, and body—is one which always intrigued me. I have sought earnestly to
        learn the difference between the three. It is easy enough to distinguish between the body and 
        the other two. But it is sometimes difficult to distinguish between the spirit and the soul.
        Nothing but the Bible can do that. Misunderstanding on this subject abounds. Much error has 
        been taught, even from the pulpit.\n\n

For years I studied the books used in various theological schools on the study of man in my search for 
        the truth in this area. I studied the books taught by the Full Gospel Bible schools. I had the 
        books used by the denomination which I had belonged to previously. But I found little satisfaction 
        from all these. They were all based on the teachings of individuals and not on the Bible.\n\n

I talked to some of the most able Bible teachers in Full Gospel circles. I talked to some who had earned 
        doctorate degrees in theology. It was surprising how little most of them knew on the subject of 
        man\'s spirit, soul, and body.\n\n

Some have said to me, I always thought the spirit and the soul were the same. I\'ve always preached it 
        that way. But I pointed out to them that they couldn\'t be the same. Otherwise why would the Bible 
        say,  For the word of God is quick, and powerful, and sharper than any two-edged sword, piercing even 
        to the dividing asunder of soul and spirit . . . . (Heb. 4:12) If they were the same, they could not 
        be divided. If they were the same, Paul would not have said,  ... I pray God your whole spirit and soul
        and body be preserved blameless unto the coming of our Lord Jesus Christ  (I Thess. 5:23).\n\n
It would be just as scriptural to say that the body and the soul are the same as it would be to say that the
        spirit and the soul are the same. In reality they are three very distinct things. After much prayer 
        and study over a long period of time I arrived at my conclusions on the three dimensions of man in 
        this way. I knew without argument that with the physical body we contact the world. The body deals 
        in the physical realm. No one will dispute that. Then,  as I studied I saw that it is the spirit of 
        man that contacts God, for God is a Spirit. Only a spirit could contact a spirit.
        The new birth is a rebirth of the human spirit, for Jesus told Nicodemus,  . . . .
        Ye must be born again (John 3:7).
        Nicodemus, being natural, could only think naturally, so he said,  How can a man be born when he 
        is old? can he enter the second time into his mother\'s womb, and be born? Jesus answered, 
        That which is born of the flesh is flesh; and that which is born of the Spirit is spirit.
        \n\nThen I decided I would go through the entire New Testament, seeing what Paul and the other
        apostles said on this subject. I found where Paul said in Romans 2:28-29,  For he is not a Jew,
        which is one outwardly;
        neither is that circumcision, which is outward in the flesh: But he is a Jew, which is one 
        inwardly; and circumcision is that of the heart, in the spirit, and not in the letter; whose 
        praise is not of men, but of God.  Paul was saying here that the spirit is the heart.\n\n

Then in I Corinthians 14:14 we read,  For if I pray in an unknown tongue, my spirit prayeth . . . . T
        he Amplified Translation reads,  My spirit (by the Holy Spirit within me prays . . . .  
        In Verse 18 Paul said,  I thank my God, I speak with tongues more than ye all. Paul used the 
        terms  my spirit  and I interchangeably.\n\n

        
Having seen that with the body we contact the physical realm and with the spirit we contact the 
        spiritual realm, that left only the soul to locate. Since the body deals with the physical 
        realm and the spirit deals with the spiritual realm, that left only one other realm that man 
        is involved in—the mental realm. So with the soul we contact the intellectual realm. This is, 
        of course, simplifying it in the extreme.
        As we go further in our study of this subject we shall delve into it more deeply.
        But here in this first chapter we are just laying the foundation.\n\n

Briefly, man\'s three-fold nature is this:\n\n

(1) Spirit\n\n\n

(2) Soul\n\n\n

(3) Body\n\n\n

The dimension of man which deals with the spiritual realm. The part of man that knows God.\n\n

The dimension of man which deals with the mental realm. Man\'s intellect. The sensibilities and will. 
        The part that reasons and thinks.\n\n

The dimension of man which deals with the physical realm. The house in which we live.\n\n

I want you to begin thinking of yourself in a new light. Don\'t think of yourself as just a physical 
        being. Think of yourself as a spirit being who possesses a soul and lives in a body.\n\n</string>


    <string name="devils_strategies">\tHOW TO STAND AGAINST \tTHE DEVIL\'S STRATEGIES \n\n</string>
    <string name="main_devils_strategies">
\nAnd do give no way to the evil one.\n
Ephesians 4:27, The Amplified Bible\n\n

If you give the devil place, he will take it. You have to stay alert and keep your shield of 
        faith high because if you don\'t, he\'ll turn around and steal back from you the ground you 
        just took.\n\n

There have been people who have received their healing and have fallen back into their old thinking 
        patterns of sickness. They let their faith down and gave the devil an opening. When he came 
        along with an old symptom, they weren\'t ready for him. They fell victim to his counterattack.\n\n

You can stand successfully against the devil\'s strategies! But before you do, you\'re going to have 
        to make three quality decisions.\n\n

First, you must make the Word of God the final authority in your life. Line up your thinking with 
        whatever the Word says.\n\n

Next, you must decide to live your life by faith in what God has said. The Bible says, \ "Faith comes
        by hearing, and hearing by the Word of God\" (Romans 10:17, New King James Version).\n\n

Finally, you must decide to live by the love of God because faith works by love. Without love, your 
        faith won\'t function. Without the Word, you can\'t have faith. So don\'t try to make one of 
        these decisions without the other two. You need to make all three of them. This lifestyle of
        the Word, faith and love keeps you in a place of resistance to the devil!\n\n

I suggest you get alone with God and pray:\n\n

In the Name of Jesus, I commit myself from this day forward to live by the Word of God, to live by my
        faith, and to live by the love of God.\n\n

Decide today to give the devil no place!\n\n

Scripture Reading:
John 15:7-12\n\n

        KENNETH COPELAND\n\n\n</string>


    <string name="praying_the_right_way">PRAYING THE RIGHT WAY PART I </string>
    <string name="main_praying_the_right_way">\tThe Genesis of Prayer.\n\n
Prayer is a result of God\’s established authority structure between heaven and earth, as well as a 
        product of His faithfulness to His Word. (Gen. 1:26-27)\n\n
The legal authority to dominate earth was given to mankind only. God did not include Himself in the
        legal authority structure over the earth. Any influence or interference from the supernatural
        realm on earth is only legal through mankind.  Ps. 8:6, Ps. 115:16, Heb. 6:17, Eph. 1;11, Isa.
        46:10-11, Isa. 55:11-12. Mat. 7:7-8, Ps.65:2\n\n
Adam had dominion upon this earth and in this world. He was originally, in a sense, god of this world.
        But Satan came and lied to Adam. Adam committed high treason and sold out to Satan. Then Satan 
        became the god of this world. Gen. 3:2-\n\n
When Adam shifted blame, he shifted power to the woman. And when the woman also shifted blame, she shifted
        power to the devil. 2 Cor. 4:4, John 14:30. -\n\n

Story... -\n\n


During the Vietnam War a nationally syndicated newspaper columnist began one column by stating that he was 
        not a Christian. He said that he was not an atheist because the atheist says there is no God.  \"I 
        suppose you would classify me an agnostic,\" he wrote.\" The agnostic says there may be a God, but if 
        there is, I don\'t know it. Actually, I am prone to believe there is a Supreme Being. I do not
        believe that everything here just happened.\n\n I believe there is a Creator somewhere. \"But I have
        never read the Bible. I do not attend church. One reason I don\'t is that what the Christians say 
        about God doesn\'t agree with what I think a Creator should be, nor with what I can see of Him in nature.
        \"Even ministers say, \'God has everything under control. He\'s running everything.\" Well, if He is, 
        He sure has things in a mess. People  are killing each other. Little children are dying. 
        Little children are hungry. Women are suffering.\n\n There are wars everywhere. \"If God has
        everything under control, do you mean God is running those wars?\"
•	But thanks be to God, Jesus has broken the devil\’s hold over the earth! He stripped the devil of
        all his power and authority (Colossians 2:15), and gave to us the same authority He has over all
        things, including the earth and the devil himself (Matthew28:18-20). Luke 10:19 
</string>

    <string name="praying_the_right_partII">WHAT\'s THEN PRAYER?</string>
    <string name="main_praying_the_right_wayII">WHAT THEN IS PRAYER?\n\n
	Prayer is man giving God the legal right and permission to interfere in earth\’s affairs.
        (Eze. 22:29-31, Mat. 16:19, Mat. 18:18-20, Lk.18:1, 1Thes. 5:17)\n\n
As John Wesley once said, \“God does nothing for humanity but in answer to prayer.\”\n\n

THE RIGHT WAYS TO PRAY \n\n
	A great many believers don\’t have successful prayer lives—and successful lives in general—because
        they simply don\’t know how or why to pray. \n\n

It is often said that the way to learn how to pray is to pray. However, this is not correct. The way to
        learn how to pray is to be taught. \n\n

\"And it came to pass, that, as He was praying in a certain place, when He ceased, one of His disciples 
        said unto Him, Lord, teach us to pray, as John also taught his disciples. And He said unto them,
        when ye pray, say...Luke 11:1-2\n\n
	Prayer is not just communication. It is having the correct approach to communicating with God,
        because it takes praying aright to be heard. James 4:2-3\n
	God doesn\'t answer prayer because you scream , whoop, holler, groan, and moan; it\'s not noise 
        that gets God\'s attention. Mat. 6:7-8.\n\n
</string>

    <string name="praying_the_right_partIII">PRAYING THROUGH THE PROMISES OF GOD.</string>
    <string name="main_praying_the_right_partIII">\tPrayer is approaching God in order to ask Him to
        accomplish His will in the Earth.\n
                    Your will be done on Earth as it is on heaven. Lk. 11:2b\n\n
Praying does not mean convincing God to do your will, but doing His will through your will. John 15:7.\n\n
This is the confidence we have in approaching God: that if we ask anything according to his will, 
        he hears us. And if we know that he hears us—whatever we ask—we know that we have what we 
        asked of him. (1 John 5:14–15) \n\n
	The power in prayer is not based on your feelings, opinions or your desires but on the word of God. 
        Prayer is communication, not emotional displays. God is not moved by your tears; He is only 
        moved when you ask according to His will.  Ps. 138:2.\n\n

	Prayer has a language and the language is in the word of God. A language is the ability to
        communicate using words or the particular words used in speech or communication. It\'s not
        possible to speak a language without understanding the language. You cannot contact God with 
        the language of today without the language of the Bible. God understands only His word. The
        Word of God is what gives worth to your prayers and qualifies you for a heavenly audience.\n\n
	Phil. 4:6, How, through the right way. John 14:6\n\n
The way is Jesus and Jesus is the word. John 14:1-6, 10:9, 1:1-1,14.\n\n
The Truth is the word. John 17:17\n\n
The life is the word. John 6:63\n\n
	God has to be true to His word, even if it means not answering the prayers that we pray. Mat. 5:8 , \n\n
	God will only do what He has said he\’ll do.  God doesn\’t answer our prayer because we asked Him. 
        He answers our prayers because we ask Him to do what he has said He will do. John 15:7\n\n
 God only watches over His word to perform it. He only fulfils his promises and not your desires and 
        your prayers. He has exalted His word above Himself. Jer. 1:12, Is a. 55:11 , Is a. 43:26.\n\n
	 If you take enough time to prepare in the Word, you will spend less time in prayers and get more 
        results eventually. Col. 3:16.\n\n
</string>


    <string name="self_dev_I">\tSELF DEVELOPMENT I </string>

    <string name="main_self_dev">
\tIt\'s  everyone\'s desire to be great in life and make significant impact in the world. We all wish
        to be great one day. We sometimes forget that greatness start from within. As novelist Leo Tolstoy said,
        Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing  himself.\”. \n That\'s our problem.
        Retired General Electric CEO Jack Welch said, \“Before you are become a leader, success is all
        about growing your self. When you become a leader, success is all about growing others.\”\n\n
This stands  to reason that, before we can impact our world and be a great person in history,  we must
        first develop ourselves. This brings us to our topic \'SELF DEVELOPMENT\'.\n\n
THE MEANING OF SELF DEVELOPMENT \n\n
Self development is also known as personal development or personal growth or self improvement. \n
Psychologists say, \"Personal development is the conscious effort to learn, grow and improve yourself by
        enhancing self awareness, knowledge and personal skills.\"
Which means  taking steps to better yourself, such as by learning new skills or overcoming bad habits.\n
Self-development is a higher calling; it is the development of your potential so that you can attain the
        purpose for which you were created. self development always has one effect: It draws you toward
        your destiny.\n\n
The pursuit of self development lies in the understanding that we have the ability to  change ourselves
        and our circumstances.\n
All improvement in your life therefore begins with an improvement in your self concept.
Your potential is limitless and investing in personal development is a way to harness your many talents.\n
You\'ll become unstoppable and you will see entire future open up in front of you if you live a goal
        and growth-oriented life.\n
I must say that, God wants us to develop[ grow, improve and become better].  Ephesians 4:14‭-‬16 MSG\n\n
No prolonged infancies among us, please. We\’ll not tolerate babes in the woods, small children who are
        an easy mark for impostors. God wants us to grow up, to know the whole truth and tell it in love—like
        Christ in everything. We take our lead from Christ, who is the source of everything we do. He keeps us
        in step with each other. His very breath and blood flow through us, nourishing us so that we will grow
        up healthy in God, robust in love.\n\n
That\'s why  Some opportunities are given only to people who have grown and developed themselves.\n\n
In Galatians 4:1‭-‬2 KJV
Now I say, That the heir, as long as he is a child, differeth nothing from a servant, though he be Lord of all;
        But is under tutors and governors until the time appointed of the father.\n\n
That\'s why even Jesus our perfect example grewand developed himself before certain privileges were
        given to him.\n\n
Luke 2:52 MSG.
 And Jesus matured, growing up in both body and spirit, blessed by both God and people.
Before this verse, the verses before says that, he was in the church and was learning. Luke 2:42-52\n\n
This stands to reason that growth is not automatic.
Just because you grow older doesn\'t mean you keep growing. Self development is a personal matter.
        Growth is personal. I  can\'t grow for you. No one can grow or improve for you. Growth is
        your responsibility.\n
Growing is a good thing, but relatively few people dedicate themselves to the process. Growth must
        be intentional—nobody improves by accident.
An unintentional life accepts everything and does nothing. An intentional life embraces only the
        things that will add to the mission of significance.
Curt Kampmeier once said, \“If you\’re going to grow, you have to be intentional.\”
When you live each day with intentionality, there\’s almost no limit to what you can do.
        Great self development requires intentional living.\n\n
The words of physicist Albert Einstein motivate me: \“The world is a dangerous place,
        not because of those who do evil, but because of those who look on and do nothing.\”
Don\'t be afraid to start something new. Zac. 4:10.\n
Rome was not built in a day. \n\n
Discover your uniqueness, then discipline yourself to develop it\n\n\n
</string>

    <string name="self_dev_II">PAY THE PRICE  II</string>
    <string name="main_self_dev_II">\t\tPAY THE PRICE ,  TRADE IMMEDIATE  PLEASURE FOR PERSONAL GROWTH.\n\n
\tGrowth is always worth the price you pay because the alternative is limited life with unfulfilled potential. 
        You have to face constant change and take risks. Embrace change.  If you fear change, then 
        you fear personal development, as self improvement is about changing yourself.\n\n
President Theodore Roosevelt boldly stated,  \“There has not yet been a person in our history who led a life of ease whose name is worth remembering.\”    It requires discipline. It takes time that you could spend on leisure activities. It costs money to buy materials. \n
You must lay aside certain sins that can impede your growth and development.\n\n


Hebrews 12:1 KJV\n
Wherefore seeing we also are compassed about with so great a cloud of witnesses, let us lay aside 
        every weight, and the sin which doth so easily beset us, and let us run with patience the 
        race that is set before us,\n\n
Be Willing To Change. If you cannot change you cannot be anything more than what you already are and 
        therefore cannot be successful in improving yourself.\n\n
INVEST INTO YOUR FUTURE. \n\n
1 Corinthians 9:24‭-‬25 AMP\n
Do you not know that in a race all the runners run [their very best to win], but only one receives 
        the prize? Run [your race] in such a way that you may seize the prize and make it yours!
        Now every athlete who [goes into training and] competes in the games is disciplined and 
        exercises self-control in all things. They do it to win a crown that withers, but we 
        [do it to receive] an imperishable [crown that cannot wither].\n\n
1 Corinthians 9:26‭-‬27 MSG\n
I don\’t know about you, but I’m running hard for the finish line. I\’m giving it everything I\’ve 
        got. No sloppy living for me! I\’m staying alert and in top condition. I\’m not going to get 
        caught napping, telling everyone else all about it and then missing out myself.\n\n
Challenge Yourself and Take Risks.  Be part of the growth mindset people. 
They view their skills and attributes as characteristics that can be learned via determined effort. 
        They aspire to modify themselves into becoming something better every time. Therefore, 
        they believe that they can get smarter, more intelligent, and more talented through putting 
        in time and effort. \n\n
BE A CONTINUAL LEARNER.\n\n
 Learning something every day is the essence of being a continual learner . I\'ve personally observed 
        that, the more you learn and grow, the greater your capacity to keep learning. That\'s why Paul
        the apostle said in Phil. 3:10....\n\n
No matter how much it costs you to keep growing and learning, the cost of doing nothing is greater.\n\n
If you stop learning, you stop leading. LEARNING IS MEANT TO BE A LIFELONG PURSUIT. Many people regard 
        learning as an event instead of a process. Education is not for a period of life but a way of life. 
        Learning is an activity that is not restricted by age. Personal development takes place over the 
        course of a person\'s entire life.\n Take responsibility for your own lifelong personal development.
        One of my mentors once said, \" anyone who stops learning is old. Whether at age 20 or 80.\" 
        The good news is that an average person who has developed the  habit of lifelong learning  will
        eventually be more advanced than the genius who has stopped learning. The payoff of continuous
        learning will last you all the days of your life. Joshua 1:8 NLT
Study this Book of Instruction continually. Meditate on it day and night so you will be sure to obey 
        everything written in it. Only then will you prosper and succeed in all you do.  The new self 
        renews as we continually learn.\n\n
Colossians 3:10 AMP.\n
and have put on the new [spiritual] self who is being continually renewed in true knowledge in the 
        image of Him who created the new self—\n\n
No matter how successful you are today, don\’t get complacent. Stay hungry. Don\'t be complacent. 
        Rick Warren says, \“The greatest enemy  of tomorrow\’s success is today\’s success.\”  
        If you\’re not moving forward as a learner, then you are moving backward as a leader.
        You may not be where you\’re supposed to be. You may not be what you want to be. 
        You don\’t have to be what you used to be . \n\n
BE TEACHABLE.\n\n
Teachability  is the desire to listen, learn, and apply. It is the willingness to learn, unlearn, and relearn.
        It is the hunger to discover and grow. Teachable people are always open to new ideas and are willing 
        to learn from anyone who has something to offer.\n  They are interested in discovery, discussion, 
        application, and growth. Listen to others, remain humble, and you will begin to learn things every 
        day that can help you expand your talent. As the old saying goes, \“There\’s a reason you have one 
        mouth but two ears.\” \n\n
Luke 2:42-52\n\n
Even if you are at the top of your field, there\'s always something to learn. Sydney Harris insisted 
        that a winner knows how much he still has to learn, even when he is considered an expert by 
        others; a loser wants to be considered an expert by others before he has learned enough to 
        know how little he knows.\” \n\n
CHOOSE A GOOD COMPANY.\n\n
 Cultivate friendships with people who challenge and add value to you, and try to do the same for them.
        It will change your life. A Spanish philosopher and writer Baltasar Gracian said, \“Make your 
        friends your teachers and mingle the pleasures of conversation with the advantages of 
        instruction.\” \n\n
John Wooden: \“Everything we know we learned from someone else!\” Listen to others, remain humble, and you 
        will begin to learn things every day that can help you expand your talent. \n\n
SURROUND YOURSELF WITH POSITIVITY\n\n
.  Find the positive aspect in everything, accepting what cannot be changed, and acting on what can,
        towards a positive result. Positive thinking lower stress,  Prevents high blood pressure,
        Boost your self -esteem, and helps you to live long. \n\n
CONQUER YOUR FEARS. \n\n
Psychologist Dr. Joyce Brothers asserts, \“The person interested in success has to learn to view 
        failure as a healthy, inevitable part of the process of getting to the top.\”  The process of
        achievement comes through repeated failures and the constant struggle to climb to a higher 
        level.\n\n\n
</string>

    <string name="STOP_COMPARING_YOURSELF">STOP COMPARING YOURSELF III</string>
    <string name="main_STOP_COMPARING_YOURSELF">\tSTOP COMPARING YOURSELF TO OTHERS AND FOCUS ON DEVELOPING YOUR SELF.\n\n
        
Dr. Myles Munroe once said, \" if you look down you\'ll be depressed. If you look around you\'ll be oppressed.
        But if you look up you\'ll be at rest.\n\n
 Ecclesiastes 11:4 AMP\n
He who watches the wind [waiting for all conditions to be perfect] will not sow [seed], and he who 
        
        looks at the clouds will not reap [a harvest].\n\n
DON\'T WASTE TIME ON THOSE WHO CRITICISE YOU.\n\n
I read a book by Archbishop Benson Idahosah in 2014 and he said something and I quote, \" I\'m busy
        doing the good. I don\'t have time to reply those who criticize me.  That\'s  keeping me going.\"  \n\n
CREATE A PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT PLAN FOR YOUR LIFE.\n\n
 A personal development plan is your guideline for your life and future success. The reason you need 
        one is because making a plan will help you make better decisions and remind yourself where 
        you want to go.\n Creating a plan for self development helps you get a better sense of control 
        over your life  and will make you better prepared for whatever comes your way. Establishing aims 
        and goals for what you want to achieve, and where you would like to go in the short term or long
        term, can improve your personal development.\n\n
BE DISCIPLINE AND FOLLOW YOUR  PLAN.\n\n
The law of consistency says that, motivation gets you going but discipline keeps you growing. Focusing
        on your own individual personal development plan enhances the qualities within you and makes your 
        dreams and aspirations turn into a reality.\n\n
CHOOSE A MENTOR TO HELP YOU GROW\n\n
Proverbs 11:14 MSG\n\n
Without good direction, people lose their way; the more wise counsel you follow, the better your chances.
Galatians 4:1‭-‬2 KJV\n
Now I say, That the heir, as long as he is a child, differeth nothing from a servant, though he be Lord of all; 
        But is under tutors and governors until the time appointed of the father.\n\n
SELF DEVELOPMENT IS VERY IMPORTANT BECAUSE; \n\n
If you\’re not moving forward as a learner, then you are moving backward as a leader.\n\n
	The only way to improve the quality of your life is to improve yourself.\n\n
	Personal development is a major time-saver. \“ The better you become, the less time it takes you
        to achieve your goals.\” ―Brian Tracy\n\n
	It put you in a fast track in your career\n\n
	It opens doors and opportunities for you\n\n
	The payoff of continuous learning will last you all the days of your life.\n\n
	Self development or self improvement touches upon all aspects of life.\n\n
	Self development increase your value. THE BETTER YOU ARE, THE GREATER YOUR VALUE TODAY. \n\n
	An investment in your growth is an investment in your ability, your adaptability, and your 
        promotability.\n\n
	self development always has one effect: It draws you toward your destiny.\n\n


Your life is before you. Fill these pages with kind acts, good thoughts, and matters of your heart. 
        Write a great story with your life.\n\n
2 Peter 1:5-7\n
Now for this very reason also, applying all diligence, in your faith supply moral excellence, 
        and in your moral excellence, knowledge, and in your knowledge, self-control, and in 
        your self-control, perseverance, and in your perseverance, godliness, and in your godliness,
        brotherly kindness, and in your brotherly kindness, love.\n
Isa 54:2  \"Enlarge the place of your tent, and let them stretch out the curtains of your habitations;
        do not spare; lengthen your cords, and strengthen your stakes\”.\n\n
</string>

    <string name="rubbed_god">HAVE YOU ROB GOD</string>
    <string name="main_rubbed_god">

HAVE YOU EVER ROBBED GOD?\n
Malachi 3:1-18\n\n
      How can man rob God? God dwells in heaven and besides He is a spirit and how can a man rob God? 
        But God told the children of Israel that they had robbed Him in tithes and offering. He said 
        they had turned aside from Him in that they had forsaken to bring their tithes and offering 
        before Him.\n\n
       The tithe is the tenth part of one\'s earnings. Abram was the first person who pay tithe to Melchizedek,
        King of Salem and priest of the most high(Hebrews 7:1-4). Such is not supposed to be eaten 
        but should be brought to the servants of God. The offering is given out of what one is convinced to give willingly. 
        These two are very necessary in the life of the believer.\n\n
      God has promised that when we give our offerings and pay the full amount of our tithe, He will 
        rebuke the devourer for our sake and open the windows of heaven and pour us a blessing. 
        That is why the Bible says there is blessing in giving than in receiving(Acts 20:35).\n\n
       Have you remembered to be faithful in tithes and offerings? If not, then you are robbing God.
        No matter how little you have, still remain faithful and give God what is supposed to be God\'s
        and you will see the hand of God upon your life. \nHe will cause a surprised increase in whatever you do. 
        Beloved in Christ, give what belongs to God to God so as not to rob God. Thank you for your understanding.\n\n
      Prayer point: Pray that God will give you the heart to be faithful in giving of tithe and offering. \n\n
      May the Lord give you the  giving heart. \n\n\n
</string>

    <string name="book_of_life">BOOK OF LIFE</string>
    <string name="main_book_of_life">\tRevelation 3:5; 20:12; 15\n
After reading our Text, I trust that you will agree with me that there will be nothing more horrible
        than to stand at the Great White Throne Judgment and find that your name has been forever
        blotted out of the Book of Life and then to immediately realize that you are hopelessly lost
        and that you will spend forever in the Lake of Fire. We are going to talk about names today…
        Your name is important.\n\n
YOU DO HAVE A NAME… Proverbs 22:1\n\n
\“A good name is rather to be chosen than great riches, and loving favour rather than silver and gold.\”\n\n
Webster\’s Dictionary tells us that a name is: a word or phrase that constitutes the distinctive
        designation of a person or thing. In the Old Testament, especially, the names were given
        to communicate the \“heart\” of the parent into the life of the child.\n For an example,
        Daniel\’s name means: \“God is my Judge\”. It was as though the parents wanted to impress
        upon Daniel that the supreme leader and judge is the Lord. Even in the New Testament,
        the name Lazarus means: \“God a help\”. In this case, I imagine that the mother of Lazarus
        could not give her son riches and perhaps very little help. As he lay at the rich man\’s
        table and his name was called, it reminded him that God was his help, even if he were only
        eating crumbs from the rich man\’s table.\n\n
A. Having a Name Signifies That You Have Lived… Jeremiah 1:5\n\n
Believing that life originates at conception, I also believe that the Lord knows you as an individual
        and knew you from the moment of conception. In an eternal sense God has always known you.
        The lord knew Jeremiah before he was in his mother\’s womb. \“Before I formed thee in the
        belly I knew thee; and before thou camest forth out of the womb I sanctified thee, and I
        ordained thee a prophet unto the nations\”.  Jeremiah 1:5.\n\n
B. Having a Name Signifies That You Are Listed… Ex 32:32\n\n
The Scriptures indicate that the Lord has written a book and it seems that this book is the Book of Life.
        Notice how Moses refers to this book when he is dealing with the rebellion of a sinful nation
        and interceding on their behalf.\n\n
\“Yet now, if thou wilt forgive their sin--; and if not, blot me, I pray thee, out of thy book which
        thou hast written.\” (Exodus 32:32)\n\n
Moses was willing to have his name blotted out of the book that the Lord had written. I believe that
        this book is the Book of Life or literally the book of living which includes every person
        conceived when we understand that life begins at conception.\n\n
C. Having a Name Signifies That You Are Loved…\n\n
I am able to say that because John 3:16 is still in the Bible. As long as there is a John 3:16 in
        the Bible and that is forever, God will love you. You are significantly loved by the Lord.
        He loves you personally. You are not a \“John Doe\” to Him. May I say it like this,
        \“To Him you are Somebody worth dying for\”…\n\n
II. YOUR NAME IDENTIFIES YOU…\n\n
A. The Stars Are Named…\n\n
We hear of Credit card theft and in association with that, we hear of identity theft.
        I am so grateful that there is no identity theft with God. Just recently,
        I read in my devotions that the Lord named all of the stars and knows them by name.
        With such a staggering large number as that, it still is no issue with God. You can be assured,
        if He knows the stars by number and then calls them all by their names (and He does),
        He certainly knows who you are. \“He telleth the number of the stars; he calleth them all by their names.\” Psalms 147:4\n\n
B. The Souls of Men Are Named…\n\n
I certainly do not pretend to know how God names us, but I can know that there are no unknowns with God.
        When He makes His book, He may name us differently than the way that we do…
        I certainly do not know. What if He took the Old Testament formula for naming us,
        as did the parents then, and then identified us by the way that we conduct ourselves?
        Have you not heard people say, \“Why, there is Mr. Big Shot or Miss Stuck up?\”
        The Lord may also have His names as such. He may call John, \“John the liar\” or \“John the
        procrastinator\”. He may have \“Hypocrite Joe\” or \“Sam the scam artist\”.
        Then there may be \“Willy Drunkard\” or \“Mary Prostitute\”. Then He may have \“Frank the Faithful\” or
        \“Arthur Longsuffering\”. I really do not know how He names us, but if He named and numbered the stars,
        He also can name us… He has you and I \“pegged\”\n\n.
</string>

    <string name="book_of_life_2">YOUR NAME IS IN A BOOK</string>
    <string name="main_book_of_life_2">A. The Book Is His…\n\n
We are living in the computer age. Those who are computer savvy will tell you that modern man has the
        capabilities of storing large bundles of information in a relative small space. 
        I am amazed at how many large volumes of books can be put on a small electronic device that will
        conveniently fit on a key chain. This is only what man is capable of doing; 
        just think what God is capable of doing. He not only records your and my names, 
        He records everything about us. There is nothing that is hidden from Him.
        In Revelation 20:12, we are told that a book (singular) is opened and before that, books (plural) were opened.
        The books contain the life evidence of every person that lived. The book contains the names of those who lived.
        Notice the Text:\n\n
11 \”And I saw a great white throne, and him that sat on it, from whose face the earth and the heaven fled away; 
        and there was found no place for them. 12 And I saw the dead, small and great, stand before God; 
        and the books were opened: and another book was opened, which is the book of life: 
        and the dead were judged out of those things which were written in the books, according to their works. 
        13 And the sea gave up the dead which were in it; and death and hell delivered up the dead which were in them: 
        and they were judged every man according to their works. 14 And death and hell were cast into the lake of fire.
        This is the second death. 15 And whosoever was not found written in the book of 
        life was cast into the lake of fire\”. Rev 20:11-15\n\n
B. The Book Is In Heaven…\n\n
By this book being in heaven that means that no one will tamper with it. You can neither add 
        to nor take away from this book. You can neither buy your way into the book nor take yourself out of the book.
        There are many living today that thinks that their money can buy anything that they need. 
        Not so! Jesus hung on an old rugged cross to pay the sin debt that He alone could pay.
        Jesus paid it all. If you are to go to heaven you must receive Him as the following 
        verse so indicates:\n\n
\“But as many as received him, to them gave he power to become the sons of God, even to them 
        that believe on his name: 13 Which were born, not of blood, nor of the will of the flesh, 
        nor of the will of man, but of God.\” John 1:12-13\n\n
IV.YOUR NAME COULD BE REMOVED…Ex. 32:33; Rev. 3:5\n\n
A. For Unbelief…\n\n
Yet now, if thou wilt forgive their sin--; and if not, blot me, I pray thee, out of thy book which thou hast written.
        33 And the LORD said unto Moses, Whosoever hath sinned against me, him will I blot out of my book. 
        (Ex 32:32-33)\n\n
He that overcometh, the same shall be clothed in white raiment; and I will not blot out his name out of the
        book of life, but I will confess his name before my Father, and before his angels. (Rev 3:5)\n\n
As much as I can tell from reading the Scriptures that pertain to the names being removed, they will only
        be removed for the terrible sin of unbelief. There is not a more wicked sin than that of unbelief. 
        It is unbelief that seals a person\’s soul in hell forever. Belief requires that you trust the Word
        of God and faith comes by the Word of God, alone. It is for this reason that there has been 
        so much tampering with the Word of God. It is for this reason that such a solemn warning is
        given at the very end of the Bible. 18 For I testify unto every man that heareth the words 
        of the prophecy of this book, If any man shall add unto these things, God shall add unto him
        the plagues that are written in this book: 19 And if any man shall take away from the words of
        the book of this prophecy, God shall take away his part out of the book of life, and out of the 
        holy city, and from the things which are written in this book.\n\n
Rev 22:18-19\n\n
B. For Eternity…\n\n
It is my belief that God has recorded all that lived proving that He is not willing that 
        any should perish, but that all should come to repentance. Even though it is not 
        God\’s will or preference for man to perish, when man refuses God\’s mercy then justice must be done.
        At the final refusal, on the part of man, I believe that God will then blot out the unbeliever thus 
        leaving a place where that person\’s name once was. When all of the names have been blotted out,
        the names that are left will then constitute The Lamb\’s Book of Life. If your name is blotted out, 
        you will be cast into the eternal Lake of Fire to burn forever…\n\n
V. WILL YOUR NAME BE IN THE LAMB’S BOOK OF LIFE...?\n\n
The Lamb\’s Book of Life is named in a way that immediately calls attention to whose Book it is and what the book contains.
        In a time sequence the Lamb\’s Book of Life appears after the Book of Life. The Lamb\’s Book is the final addition, 
        for it will only contain the redeemed.\n\n
A. Only Those Who Are Redeemed…\n\n
This is such an important question and the way that you answer it will determine where you spend your forever eternity. 
        Forever is a long time. What is it that you are either doing or are involved in that will be worth spending 
        eternity in the Lake of Fire over?\n\n
B. Only Those Who Have Repented…\n\n
You can be saved today by trusting and believing on the Lord Jesus Christ if you are willing to repent
        of your sins…\n\n
When one repents he turns from his sins and with a desire an attitude to turn from his sins,
        he turns to the Saviour. Will you turn to Him today?\n\n
Scriptures: Exodus 32:32, Jeremiah 1:5, John 1:12-13, John 3:16, Proverbs 22:1, Psalms 147:4, 
        Revelation 20:11-15, Revelation 20:12, Revelation 3:5, Revelation 3:5-20:5\n\n
</string>

    <string name="why_you_were_born">Why Were You Born?</string>
    <string name="main_why_you_were_born">Why Were You Born?\n\n

No one can make you feel inferior without your consent.\n Eleanor Roosevelt\n\n

The people I have met who are progressing in life and affecting other people\’s lives—people like 
        Dale Carnegie, a tremendous man who has touched many people\’s lives, or Robert Schuler, 
        who is ministering to people all over the world to help them improve their self-esteem—all 
        seem to say the same thing: If you feel good about yourself, you will feel good about other people.
        In other words, only after you see yourself as a worthwhile person can you appreciate others 
        as worthwhile people.\n\n

If you feel good about yourself, you will feel good about other people.\n\n

That\’s a very important insight because many people do not feel good about themselves. They look at 
        themselves and wonder why God made them; or they doubt that anyone can find any good in them.
        But remember, God sees what others, and we ourselves, can\’t see. God\n
looks at us and sees that we are worth feeling good about. We are special to God. We are valuable and 
        important.\n\n

GOD PLANNED YOUR LIFE\n\n

The crowning work of creation came on the sixth day when God created human beings. As He looked around Him, 
        God pronounced His creation to be good. That includes you! God looked at the man and the woman 
        He had made and declared them to be \“very good.\”

God has a good attitude toward you. He created you in His image and drew you out of Himself. Before 
        you were born, you were in God. Part of His potential has been placed within you.\n\n

Do you remember the verse we suggested could be considered as the first verse in the Bible? Before 
        the beginning was, God is (Genesis 1:0). God is so big He began the beginning. 
        There could not be a beginning without God, because God got start started.
        Before start started, however, God had a finished plan for your life. 
        Your potential is not a trial and error experience. God designed 
        and predetermined you to be a success story.\n

God designed and predetermined you to be a success story.\n\n

Psalm 139,  tells us that God planned each of your days before you were even born.
        Before you were formed, God knew you. He took great care in creating you. 
        No part of your being was made without God\’s knowledge and careful concern. 
        God wants each of us. He gives us what no other part of His creation received:
        His breath of life (Genesis 2:7).\n\n




        You Are Not a Mistake\n\n

Have you ever felt like you were a mistake? Have your parents told you they wished you had never been
        born? Are you a child whose parents have told you: \“I wish you would have died when
        you were a baby\”?\n\n

You may have come into this world as the result of a rape. Your mother may have hated you in the
        womb because you reminded her of a man she wished to forget. But the fact that you were
        conceived is more important than how you were conceived. People go around dealing with how
        things happened, but God is simply concerned with the fact that He allowed your conception
        to happen.\n\n

Now when I say allow, I\’m talking about the fact that you were conceived. You may be a bastard,
        conceived out of wedlock. Being omnipotent, God had the power to prevent your conception.
        Yet God allowed it because He wanted you to show up. You are here because God wanted you to
        be born. How you came isn\’t important. What matters is that you are here. And if you are here,
        God created you with care (Psalm 139:13).\n\n

You are here because God wanted you to be born.\n\n

King David doesn\’t describe your mother in Psalm 139—she may have been an old alcoholic or a
        drug addict, a bastard or a prostitute. He is concerned with you. He describes how God knit
        you together in your mother\’s womb without describing what that womb was like.
        The womb in which you were knit together is no longer important. You are important.
        Your very existence means God wants you to exist. You are somebody special simply
        because you were born.\n\n

God saw you in your mother\’s womb when you were a tiny babya one-centimeter embryo.
        He looked into the secret place in your mother\’s womb and saw you. From the second
        your father\’s sperm and your mother\’s egg joined to form a child, God tenderly created you
        and watched you grow. God never would have allowed the sperm and the egg to come together
        if He had not planned for you to be born.\n\n

My frame was not hidden from You when I was made in the secret place. When I was woven together in
        the depths of the earth, Your eyes saw my unformed body (Psalm 139:15-16).\n\n

Although some parents feel their baby is a mistake, their thoughts are not true. God planned for
        that baby to be born. The manner in\n
which the child was conceived may not have been in God\’s plan, but the child himself is surely
        part of God\’s plan.\n\n

Those of you who were brought up in a nice family with a mother and a father who love you may not
        understand those who have been put down by their family since the day of their birth.
        You may not understand how important it is for them to know that they are not mistakes.
        Be patient with them. Help them to see that God designed them long before they were born!
        Every child who comes into this world comes as a setup from God. That little boy or girl
        doesn\’t need to arrive to see what is going to happen, because the happening was already
        set up before he or she came.\n\n

</string>

    <string name="why_were_you_born_II">GOD HAS A BOOK ON YOU</string>
    <string name="born_why_were_you_born_II">GOD HAS A BOOK ON YOU\n\n

All the days ordained for me were written in Your book before one of them came to be (Psalm 139:16).\n\n

God designed you to be somebody. He looked at your unformed body and declared, \“This child is good.\” All His plans for your life were set out long before you took a breath. He wrote out the order of your days before you lived even one day (Psalm 139:16). There\’s a book on you. Some chapters God wrote about you haven\’t even been touched yet.\n\n

Some of you are playing around in the index or you have spent years in the table of contents. Perhaps you are 30 years old and you still don\’t know God\’s plan for your life. That\’s playing around on the contents page. You are 30 years old and still wondering what you are supposed to be. You haven\’t even started yet.\n\n

Others have jumped ahead of God\’s plan. Though His design calls for you to be married in chapter 17, you got married in chapter two. You have ignored the things God wanted you to learn and experience in chapters 2 through 16 so you would be prepared for marriage in chapter 17. You have missed out on many experiences and discoveries because you moved ahead of God\’s schedule.
Some people are so busy peeking into chapter 17 they don\’t have time to live chapters 2 and 3 and 4…. Or perhaps you have pulled chapter 17 into chapter 2 so that the rest of the book is destroyed. You will never have the opportunity to experience all the chapters if you pull parts of later chapters into the early ones.\n\n

God Offers You a Rewrite\n\n

God wants to take you back to the beginning, because His plans far outreach your plans. His design for your life is so great that King David describes it as vast (Psalm 139:17). You are thinking about being a teacher while God wants you to open a school. You have plans to be a clerk while God wants you to own the store. You want to work in a neighbouring town while God wants you to go to Africa. You often cheat yourself because you don\’t realize the potential you have. Why settle to be a doorman when God wants you to own the house? David says it this way: \“God, when I look at your thoughts in the book on me, it\’s like all the sands in the ocean. Your thoughts are endless. I can\’t fathom your confidence in me.\”\n\n

God designed you to live out the careful plans He prepared for you. You are made in God\’s image. The plan He wrote for you is perfect and right. No detail or part is missing. You have the potential to live out all that God has planned for your life—but only if you accept Jesus Christ as your Saviour and Lord. That\’s the first step toward understanding why you were born.\n\n

Though you\’ve messed up God\’s perfect plan for your life, He graciously offers to write another book for you. It probably won\’t be the best-seller the first book was designed to be, but at least God gives you the chance to start over. He comes and puts you back in chapter one so you can live the many details of His plan. That\’s what being born again is all about. It\’s the opportunity to start over—it\’s finally getting back to the first chapter of God\’s book on you. God has great plans for you that\’s why He gave you life. Self-acceptance is the key to healthy self-esteem. Accept yourself as God made you. Allow His power to
transform your weakness, rather than belittling yourself when you make mistakes.\n\n

BORN TO EXPOSE HIS NATURE\n\n

Not only did God carefully plan for the details of your life, He also determined how your life would fit into His total plan for man. Part of the answer to the why of our birth is revealed in God\’s desire that we should show forth His glory. The glory of God is the excess of His nature. It\’s all the potential of our omnipotent God that has not yet been revealed. He\’s full of so much more than we can think or imagine and He\’s waiting to use us to realize that potential.\n\n

Now to Him who is able to do immeasurably more than all we ask or imagine, according to His power that is at work within us, to Him be glory in the church and in Christ Jesus throughout all generations, for ever and ever! Amen (Ephesians 3:20-21).\n\n

Throughout the Bible, God tells us to make His name great in the earth. Praise and thanks are due God\’s name, which is great and awesome (Psalm 44:8, 99:3). His name is to be proclaimed among the nations (Malachi 1:11) as well as in Israel (Psalm 76:1). His name is holy (Luke 1:49; Psalm 99:3) and mighty in power (Jeremiah 10:6). Everything is done for \“His name’s sake.\” To understand this concept, we must also understand that the Hebrew concept of \“name\” literally is synonymous with the object. In other words, the name of the thing is the thing. Therefore, the name of God is Himself, and He is His name. To glorify His name, then, means exposing His nature.\n\n

God created you to bring glory to His name. His predestined plan for your life was designed to bring Him glory. He knows there is more to you than we can see because He placed part of Himself in you. His plan for your life is part of His creative work—through you God wants to continue the birth of His potential. Because you share God\’s omnipotent nature, Jesus said you can do even greater things than He did, if you only believe (Mark 11:23).\n\n

KNOCK THE LIMITS OFF YOUR LIFE\n\n

The concept of Mark chapter 11 is that if you ask anything—if you can believe what you desire hard enough—God says it will be done. Somehow God gives us a little glimpse into our potential. He comes into our situation as if He\’s disturbed. God is disappointed in the human race. It\’s almost as though God looks at the ideas He stored in us and says with a voice of disappointment, \“If you only knew what you can do.\” That\’s the attitude of God toward you and me. God is totally disappointed in us because He knows what we can do. But we don\’t. And so He says to us: \“All things are possible if you\’d just believe, dummy.\” He\’s always knocking the limits off our lives.\n\n

Too often we are not willing to believe like God defines believe. God does not say, \“Everything is possible if you get the idea.\” Things don\’t become reality because we have an idea. We have to believe in the idea. We have to believe we can do it by committing ourselves to it—abandoning ourselves to it—even if it costs us our lives. \n Tha\t’s what it takes to believe in the Lord Jesus Christ—to lose our lives…to abandon ourselves. \nWe must say, \“I\’m going to go into eternity believing in Jesus. I\’m not sure what\’s out there, but I\’m going to ride on that Name and that atonement.\”\n\n

God isn\’t impressed by your dreams. Most of us never wake up long enough to do anything with our dreams. You may have great dreams for your life, but you prefer to stay asleep because when you wake up reality says, \“Okay, let\’s get to work.\” It\’s easier to dream an idea than to work it out. \nEverything is possible if you will abandon yourself to an idea enough that you are willing to lose your life for it. Thinking is great.\n But all things are possible when we believe. Jesus said in Mark chapter 11, \“Whatever you desire when you pray, believe you\’ll receive it, and you will have it.\” The word desire is the key. Being interested in or attracted to something is not desiring it. \nTo desire means \“to crave for something at the expense of losing everything.\”\n\n

Everything is possible if you will abandon yourself to an idea enough that you are willing to lose your life for it.\b\n

God\’s work in creation began with a plan. God conceived in His mind what He wanted before speaking His creations into visible form. By the time God was ready to speak, it was just a matter of taking what was in the plan and putting it on the site.\n\n

</string>


    <string name="who_are_you">FROM THOUGHT TO ACTION</string>
    <string name="main_who_are_you">FROM THOUGHT TO ACTION\n\n

A thought is a silent word, so a word is an exposed thought. Everything in life starts in the thought
        form—it\’s a thought first. After it\’s said, it is no longer a thought. It becomes a word.\n\n

The next step is an idea. An idea is the concept of the thought—it has moved into a reality.
        Ideas are potentials.\n\n

The third level of operation is what I call imagination. Imagination changes an idea into a plan.
        If you have an idea it can come and go. You have many ideas in a day—what to cook, what to wear, what to do.
        You may decide the night before what you are going to wear in the morning and then wake up
        with a different idea. Ideas change. \nBut if an idea develops into an imagination,
        it means the idea has become a plan. It is still not written or drawn, but it is in your head.
        Imagination is therefore a plan that is not documented. It is a visual display of your thoughts and ideas.
        Ephesians 3:20 challenges us to believe God is able and willing to do \“exceeding abundantly far
        beyond all we can think or imagine.\” He dares us to use our imaginations.\n\n

If you want to be successful in life, take your ideas and turn them into imagination; then take
        imagination and duplicate it physically. Put it down. Let it become a plan of action.\n\n

Followers, Dreamers, Visionaries, and Missionaries\n\n

Many people never get beyond the idea stage.\n That\’s sad. They are usually followers.
        The people who get to the imagination stage often
talk a lot but they do nothing. They are dreamers. But when a man or woman takes his imagination
        and puts it on paper, you are looking at a visionary who is becoming a missionary.
        Visionaries see great things in their minds. Many visionaries are in the graveyard.
        They had visions, but their visions never made it to mission. When a visionary becomes a
        missionary, you have a man or woman who is going to change the world.\n\n

MAKE PLANS…SET GOALS\n\n

God wants us to become people who have plans. He says, \“Use your imagination. I won\’t give you a
        thought if you can\’t do it. If you think it, I\’m ready to do it.\” Plans are documented imaginations.
        If you can document an imagination, you\’ve developed a plan for action.\n\n

If you are having problems in your life, I mean real problems, you probably don\’t have a piece of paper
        on which you have documented your plans for the next five years. If you are disillusioned with
        lifebored and confused—I can almost guarantee that you don\’t know what is going on in your life.
        You\’re just living from day to day in the absence of a concrete, documented plan by which to live.
        You\’ve been dealing with the same issues and habits and struggles for years.
        You slide forward a little only to slide backward again. \n Whenever things get hard,
        you start reminiscing about \“the good old days\” and fall back into habits you had conquered.\n\n

If there is no goal in front of you, you’ll check the hazardous holes behind you.
        If there is no vision in front of you to pull you on, you will be dragged back to the path you know well.
        If your imagination does not become documented, it will soon ferment into vapor and disillusionment.\n\n

Let me explain. If you do not have a paper on which you have written a general plan for your life, you may
        decide something one minute only to change it five minutes later. You will be confused,
        disoriented, misguided and frustrated. Progress requires a plan of action.
        Ideas must be put down if they are to influence the way you live.\n\n

Many of us plan our meals for the next week, but we have nothing planned for our lives.
        The food we eat just goes away—it doesn\’t touch the future.\n\n

Stop. Set your course. Imagine into your future as far as you can. Chart what you are going to do for
        the next five months…twelve months…two years. Start imagining what you want to be…what you
        want to accomplish…where you want to go…who you want to influence.
        Do something and then put your plan in a convenient location so you can check your progress,
        seeing how close you are to your next goal.\n\n

You will be amazed how that will make you work every day.
        It will encourage you to move. You will begin to see God\’s power at work within you,
        and that will motivate you even more. Don\’t worry how you are going to meet all your goals. God says,
        \“You make the plan and I will give the answer how it will be accomplished.\”\n\n

God created you to change the world. He carefully designed a plan for your life that allows you to
        share in His work of creation. Because you were made in God\’s image, you share His potential
        to be and do much more than is visible now. Everything you see was originally a thought in the
        mind of God—an invisible idea that God worked into sight. Make a plan.
        Give yourself something to be motivated toward. As you dream, think, imagine, and plan who you want to be,
        you will begin to see why God created you and the work He has designed you to do.
        You are destined by God to reveal His glory—His very nature.\n\n

PRINCIPLES\n\n

You are worth feeling good about because God wanted you to be born.\n\n

God has a detailed plan for your life.\n\n

The first step in living out God\’s plan is accepting Jesus Christ as your Savior and Lord.\n
God created you with a part of His potential so you could expose and share in His glory.\n\n

God\’s glory is the excess of His potential—His many plans that wait to be revealed through us.\n\n

Develop a plan for your life that fulfills some of the possibilities God placed within you before you were born.
        Then believe and work them into existence.\n\n
</string>


    <string name="the_real_you">THE REAL YOU</string>


    <string name="the_real_you_main">THE REAL YOU \n\n
Who you are is related to where you came from.\n\n

MANY LOOK, FEW SEE\n\n

Asculptor works in a very interesting way. I\’m an artist of sorts, so I have a bit of an
        understanding how artists work. One thing I have learned is that you never argue with 
        an artist until he is finished. Don’t discuss anything with a painter or a sculptor until 
        his work is completed. An artist can be very rude if you disturb him before he has 
        accomplished what he intends to do, because he sees differently than those who are not artists.\n\n

An artist can walk by the stone in your front yard and see a figure in it. He may stop by your house
        and beg you for a stone you have walked past many times without noticing. 
        The dogs may have been doing stuff on it. You may even have been planning
        to get rid of it because it\’s a nuisance. But the artist walks into your yard and sees 
        something beautiful in that stone beyond what you can imagine.\n\n

Two months later when the artist invites you to his workshop he says, \“Do you see that? 
        Do you know where that came from?\”\n\n

\“England or France?\” you ask.\n\n

\“No,\” says the artist. \“It came from your yard.\”\n\n

\“Do you mean…?\” \“Yes.\”\n\n

\“Five hundred dollars, please.\”\n\n

You were sitting on $500. The dogs were doing stuff on $500. But you couldn\’t see the potential 
        in the rock.\n\n

YOU ARE NOT JUNK\n\n

There are many people who are being passed by because others don\’t see what is in them. But God has
        shown me what\’s in me, and I know it is in you too. My job is to stop you and say: \“Can 
        you see what\’s in you? Do you know your potential? Do you know that you are not 
        just someone born in a ghetto over the hill? There\’s a wealth of potential in you.\”\n\n

A sculptor sees so differently. They say Michelangelo used to walk around a block of marble 
        for days—just walking around it, talking to himself. First he would see things in the rock; 
        then he would go and take them out.\n\n

Insight like that of a sculptor is seen in the Bible. When the world dumps and rejects you, 
        and you land on the garbage heap of the world, God walks along and picks you up. 
        He looks deep within you and sees a person of great worth.\n\n

Don\’t ever let anybody throw you away. You are not junk. When God looks at you, 
        He sees things that everybody else ignores. You are worth so much that Jesus went to 
        Calvary to salvage and reclaim you. The Spirit of God connected to your spirit is the 
        only true judge of your worth. Don\’t accept the opinions of others because they 
        do not see what God sees.\n\n

When God looks at you, He sees things that everybody else ignores.\n\n

GOD LOOKED AND SAW…\n\n

God looked at Adam and saw a world. He looked at Abraham and saw nations. 
        In Jacob, a deceiver, He saw a Messiah. In Moses the murderer, God saw a deliverer. 
        Can you imagine looking at a stammering young man and seeing the greatest leader in history?\n\n

God saw a king in a shepherd boy. When the Israelites wanted a king, God sent Samuel to the home of Jesse.
        When Jesse heard why Samuel was there, he dressed up all his sons—the handsome one, 
        the tall one, the curly-haired one, the strong one, the muscular one. All the sons of 
        Jesse twirled out before Samuel, from the greatest to the least. With his vase of anointing oil, 
        Samuel watched Jesse’s show as he presented his sons: \“This is my intelligent son who 
        graduated from the University of I Don’t Know What.\” After the guy gave a speech, Samuel said, 
        \“No.\” The next son came out dressed like Pat Paulson and God said, \“No.\” 
        A third son gave a nice speech about philosophy and again God said, \“No.\” 
        Finally, after Jesse had paraded all of his sons before him, Samuel said, \“I\’m sorry. 
        None of these is God\’s choice for king. Do you have any other sons?\”\n\n

Then Jesse said, \“Yes…well no. I just remembered. I do have a little boy, my youngest son. 
        He\’s just a little runt who\’s out taking care of the sheep. He\’s not dressed 
        up like my other sons, nor have his hands been manicured and his body scented with 
        perfumes from the East. This guy\’s really smelly because he\’s been out with the sheep 
        for quite some time.\”\n\n

\“Bring him,\” Samuel replied. \“Let me look at him.\”\n\n

So Jesse sent for his youngest son. When Samuel saw Jesse\’s youngest son walk into the house, 
        a little boy, he began to unscrew the lid of his vase. \“I think I have found the guy 
        I\’m looking for,\” Samuel\n
said. (Notice that God chose the son who was out working. He was busy. God chooses busy people.)\n\n

Most of us are like Jesse. We look, but we don\’t see. Were you the black sheep in your family? 
        (You know God likes sheep.) Has your family told you that you are a nobody? Have you been 
        put off and put out and told so many times that you will amount to nothing that you have 
        begun to believe it? Do you feel like the black sheep?\n\n

You are probably the one God is waiting for in the house. God sees things deep within you that 
        others can\’t see. They look at you and see a nobody; God looks at you and sees a worthwhile somebody. 
        You may spend your whole life competing with others—trying to prove that you are somebody—and still 
        feel like nobody. Be free from that today! You do not have to live with that any longer. 
        You don’t have to try to be somebody, because you are somebody.\n\n
</string>


    <string name="you_came_out_of_god">YOU CAME OUT OF GOD</string>
    <string name="main_you_came_out_of_god">YOU CAME OUT OF GOD\n\n

When God created the heavens and the earth, He first decided what He wanted to make something out 
        of and then He spoke to that source. When God wanted plants He spoke to the dirt. When God 
        wanted fish He spoke to the waters. When God wanted animals He spoke to the ground.
        Whatever God spoke to became the source from which the created thing came.\n\n

Plants thus came from the dirt, fish from the water and animals from the ground. Furthermore, 
        plants return to the dirt, fish return to the sea and animals return to the ground when they die.\n\n

All things have the same components and essence as their source. What God created is, in essence, 
        like the substance from which it came. That means plants are 100 percent dirt because they came from dirt.
        Animals are 100 percent dirt because they came from the ground. If we would take an animal apart,
        we would come up with genuine dirt. If we would put a plant under a microscope and decipher 
        all the different\n
components, we would find that everything in that plant is in dirt, because the plant is dirt.
        God called it from the dirt.\n\n

Not only are all things composed of that from which they came, they must also remain attached to 
        that source in order to live. All things must be maintained and sustained by where they came from. 
        The minute a plant decides it doesn\’t like the earth anymore, it dies. The minute the fish decide 
        they are tired of water, they die. The minute animals decide, \“We don\’t want to eat any more dirt,\” 
        they begin to die.\n\n

Thus, whatever God created came from that to which He spoke. All things were created by God\’s word to a source. 
        The source of the creation also becomes, then, the essence of that creation.
        All things are composed of whatever they came from and hence contain the potential of that source. 
        That means plants only have the potential of the soil. Animals only have the potential of dirt.\n\n

All things are composed of whatever they came from and hence contain the potential of that source.\n\n

When God wanted fish, He spoke to the water. When He wanted animals, He spoke to the dirt. 
        When God created human beings, He spoke to Himself.\n\n

Then God said, \“Let Us make man in Our image, in Our likeness…\” So God created man in His own image, 
        in the image of God He created him; male and female He created them (Genesis 1:26-27).\n\n

God created you by speaking to Himself. You came out of God and thus bear His image and likeness.\n\n

LOOK AT THE INVENTOR, NOT THE INVENTION\n\n

Never use the creation to find out who you are, because the purpose of something 
        is only in the mind of the One who made it. That is one of the reasons why God has a 
        tremendous problem with idol worship. How can you identify your ability by worshipping a 
        snake? How can\n\n

you find out your worth by believing that you will come back as a rat or a roach? How dare 
        you believe that your purpose for existence can be discovered in a relationship with a 
        wooden statue? You will never know yourself by relating to the creation, only to the Creator. 
        The key to understanding life is in the source of life, not in the life itself.\n\n

Many of the inventions man has produced would be misunderstood if only the invention were considered 
        and not the intention of the inventor. In other words, the man who created the refrigerator
        had in his mind what it was supposed to be used for. He did not intend that it 
        should be used for a trap in the backyard for a kid to be locked in and die from suffocation. 
        Even though thousands of children have died in refrigerators, that was not the inventor’s intention.\n\n

The automobile is tearing out lampposts all over the world and destroying people\’s homes and lives. But Mr. 
        Ford, who first developed the assembly line to mass produce the automobile, never thought about it that way. 
        He was thinking about transporting people and helping the human race to become a mobile community. 
        He started us to thinking about trolleys and trains and buses. 
        The many people who died through accidents and derailments were not part of his intention. 
        They were not in his mind when he designed his famous T. Ford automobile.\n\n


YOU HAVE PART OF GOD\n\n

You will never discover who you were meant to be if you use another person to find yourself. 
        You will never know what you can do by using what I\’ve done to measure your ability. 
        You will never know why you exist if you use my existence to measure it. 
        All you will see is what I\’ve done or who I am. If you want to know who you are, look at God. 
        The key to understanding life is in the source of life, not in the life itself. You are who you 
        are because God took you out of Himself. If you want to know who you are, you must look at the
        Creator, not the creation.\n\n

There are three words we use to describe God. First, God is omniscient—which means He is all knowing. 
        Second, God is omnipresent which means God is present everywhere. Third, God is\n
omnipotent—which means God is always potent. God is always full of power—He has in Him the potential 
        for everything. From the beginning, God gave that same ability to be potent to all His creation. 
        He planted within each person or thing He created—including you—the ability to 
        be much more than it is at any one moment. Thus God created you to be omni-potent.\n\n

That is not to say we are equal to God. No. What I am saying is that the word omnipotent relates 
        not only to God, but to us as well. We are always full of potential. Our potential is the 
        dormant ability, reserved power, untapped strength and unused success God designed into each of us.
        What I see when I look at you is not all you are. It is only what you have become so far. 
        Your potential is much greater than what you are right now. What you will become 
        is much more than we could ever believe now. You are somebody because you came out of God, 
        and He leaked some of Himself into you.\n\n
</string>


    <string name="GOD_PRONOUNCES_WHAT_HE_SEES">GOD PRONOUNCES WHAT HE SEES</string>
    <string name="main_GOD_PRONOUNCES_WHAT_HE_SEES">GOD PRONOUNCES WHAT HE SEES\n\n

How you feel or what others say about you is not important. You are who God says you are;
        He sees in you more than you can possibly imagine. Your potential is limited only by God,
        not others.\n\n

Coward or Warrior?\n\n

God came to a frightened young man named Gideon. Gideon obviously thought God was talking to
        someone else when the angel of the Lord called him a mighty warrior (Judges 6:12).
        The angel didn\’t say, \“Oh, coward. Do you know you have strength?\” Nor did the angel say,
        \“Oh black man, do you know that you can be like the white man?\” The angel just came in
        and announced what he saw: \“Oh mighty man of war power.\” That means \“Oh great warrior.\”\n\n

Think about it. Warrior? Gideon was hiding from the enemy trying to separate some wheat from the
        chaff so he wouldn\’t starve. He was doing it underground so no one could see him.
        When the angel said,\n

\“You are a brave man,\” Gideon started looking around to see who the angel was talking to.\n\n

God never tells us what others see. He never calls us what others call us. Gideon thought he was a coward.
        God knew him to be a great warrior and pronounced what He saw.\n\n

Flaky, Flaky\n\n

God also saw in Peter what others failed to see. His given name was Simon, which means meek.
        (Literally it means \“unstable, flaky, leaf.\”) When Jesus met Simon, he was the flakiest,
        leafiest man you ever met. He was always going with the wind—changing his mind.
        But God saw a stone in the leaf. The first time Jesus met Peter, He changed Peter\’s name
        from Simon (leaf) to Peter (stone). Although Simon was an unstable guy, Jesus said,
        \“I\’m going to change your name. Your name is Peter.\” Peter acted like a leaf
        throughout Jesus\’ earthly ministry. Still Jesus called him rock every morning.
        Jesus saw in Peter something his mother had not seen. He kept chipping until finally,
        at Pentecost, Peter\’s true nature was revealed.\n\n

STOP BELIEVING WHAT OTHERS SAY\n\n

Too often we believe the lies we are told. We believe that we are \“no good\” and worthless.
        Jesus says, \“Not so. I came to show you that you are more than you think you are.\”
        You are the image of God.\n\n

God always sees what men and women only look at. In a manger, God saw a King…in a servant,
        a Savior…in a sacrifice, salvation…in a crucifixion, a resurrection. In death, God was working
        at life; in defeat, He was looking at victory. What you or I, or your country or my country,
        looks like is not what God sees. God looks beyond the surface to the potential deep within.
        That is God\’s way of thinking about everything. Beyond the immediate troubles God sees success,
        and He continues to call it forth until what He sees becomes reality.
Remember that the seed of every tree is in the fruit of the tree. That means the blessings of the
        Third World nations are in the Third World nations, and the prosperity of America is in America.
        When we become concerned about our individual lives or the corporate life of our countries,
        we come up with all kinds of schemes and plans to solve the problem.\n\n But the answer
        is not in a multitude of systems and programs. The answer is right inside of us. It\’s our
        attitudes that make the difference. No one can make you rowdy or careless or thoughtless.
        You are rowdy and careless and thoughtless because you choose to be. So stop it! Stop
        being rowdy…stop being careless…stop being thoughtless. Only you can control how you act.
        You\’ve got the potential to be considerate and sensitive.\n\n

God saw in Peter something that Peter had never seen in himself. Peter was so busy agreeing with
        what others called him that he missed his true potential. When we start believing what others
        call us, we are in big trouble. Then we throw our hands up in despair and refuse to try. People
        call us lazy, so we become lazy. People call us careless or stupid or clumsy, so we become careless
        or stupid or clumsy. Watch it! What others look at is not important. Who we are depends on what
        we see.\n\n

Do you believe you could walk into a prison and meet some of the greatest men and women in the world?
        Can you think that way? They made a mistake. They made a misjudgment. They made poor decisions.
        But that doesn\’t invalidate their potential. It doesn\’t destroy who they can be.
        In that jail there may be a murderer on death row. But when God looks at that person,
        He doesn\’t see a murderer; He sees an author or a leader or a great world changer.\n\n

Many times God is in disagreement with the people closest to you. He may even be in
        disagreement with you, because the only person God agrees with is Himself—only He
        knows your true potential. Have you failed? Go to God. He\’ll call you \“success\”
        and keep calling you \“success\” until you feel it. That\’s what Jesus did for
        Peter.\n\n  </string>


    <string name="what_does_god_see_in_you">WHAT DOES GOD SEE IN YOU?</string>
    <string name="main_what_does_gog_see_in_you">


WHAT DOES GOD SEE IN YOU?\n\n

I wonder what God sees as He walks around you. I\’m sure He sees beautiful things in you,
        but you are believing what other people are saying. People say: \“You are no good.
        You\’ll never be somebody.\” But God is saying: \“I see a jewel.\” We are diamonds in the rough.
        Just keep on believing that. Keep on moving forward to your goal. Remember
        that there is something in you more precious than what others have said about you.
        The sculptor never gives up until he gets out of the rock what he sees.\n\n

There is something in you more precious than what others have said about you.\n\n

I have a piece of wooden sculpture in my home that I did about 15 years ago.
        The sculpture isn\’t what I intended it to be because as I was chiseling out
        the image that I had seen in the tree, part of it was knocked off by too much pressure.
        Because that part dropped off, I could no longer create the image that I had intended.
        So I looked at the piece of wood again. I walked around it thinking, \“I\’ve gotta
        change my concept a little.\” I had to rethink how to retain the beauty of the sculpture though
        I had lost an important part of the wood.\n\n

Eventually, I modified my design. But I am the only person who knows that piece of sculpture was
        made from a modified design. The modification is not evident in the finished form.
        If I showed you the piece, you wouldn\’t even notice what I\’m talking about.
        People have admired that piece of wood for many years. They look at it and say,
        \“Wow! This is beautiful.\” And I never tell them that what they see is not what
        they were originally supposed to see.\n\n

That piece of sculpture sitting in my home reminds me of your life and mine. Parts of our
        lives have been knocked off by our past. We\’ve done some dumb things that have messed up
        the beauty God intended. But look what God has done. He\’s saved us. Instead of discarding us
        because we have not turned out like He intended us to be, He has taken us—including our marred
        and chipped and rusted and\n
knocked off past—and formed us into something beautiful. When people see us now, they won’t believe
        what we used to be. And God will never tell them. Hallelujah! When people look at you and think
        you are the best thing that ever came down the pike, don\’t tell them what you used to be. Just say,
        \“Thank you very much. The Chief Sculptor had His hands on me.\” God can bring beauty out of your mistakes.
        He can take what you have messed up and bless it up. He can take the thing that seemed impossible to you and
        form it into something beautiful.\n\n

In every piece of stone a sculptor sees a figure. But we never see it until he takes it out.
        Whereas we may see only an old stump of a tree on the side of the road,
        a wood sculptor sees a beautiful piece that we would pay thousands of dollars to own.
        What looks like garbage to the nonartistic person is a treasure to the artist.\n\n

CHRIST IS IN YOU\n\n

I wonder what God sees when He looks at you. I believe He sees Christ. When God looks at you,
        He does not see you. He sees Christ. Paul, when writing to the Colossian church,
        proclaimed that God had chosen to make known a mystery.\n\n

To them God has chosen to make known among the Gentiles the glorious riches of this mystery,
        which is Christ in you, the hope of glory (Colossians 1:27).\n\n

The mystery is that Christ is in you. That is your hope of glory. This suggests, then, that our
        task is not to get Christ into us, but out of us. Please get this into your minds.
        What God sees when He looks at you is Christ.\n\n

Our task is not to get Christ into us, but out of us.\n\n

Most of us want to be like Jesus. That\’s not what God wants. God wants us to be like Christ.
        Jesus came to show us what Christ looks like when He takes on human form. But it is
        Christ that God\’s looking at.\n
God sees Christ in you. That\’s the hope of glory—Christ in you. Let me explain.\n\n

Christ is the image of God. The word image does not mean \“a statue of something.\” It means \“the
        essence of the being.\” Christ is the image of God. That means when God created you,
        He created you in His image, and His image is Christ. That\’s why the Bible never calls us
        the Body of Jesus. Jesus was the human manifestation of the heavenly Christ. We humans on
        earth, with all our fallibilities and weaknesses—God pronounces on us: \“You are the body
        of Christ.\”\n\n

In other words, Christ is in us somewhere. Christ is in me. Christ is in you. God knows He is there.
        His image is there. So God called us Christ.\n\n

If we go to God and say, \“God, please introduce me to your people,\” God will say, \“Sure.
        Here is Christ.\” But we\’ll say, \“No. No. No. I want to meet Christ,\” to which God will reply,
        \“Sure. Here\’s Christ\” as He shows us the Church. When we want to meet Christ, God will show
        us the Church. But we can\’t accept this because we think Christ is in heaven. No, He isn\’t.
        Jesus is in heaven. Christ is sitting in your clothes, living in the body of the believer.
        Christ is the essence of God—He’s God Himself.\n\n

God intended for you to be created in His image. Although you may say, \“I want to be
        like Jesus,\” God says, \“There\’s something deeper.\” You were lost and Jesus came to bring you back.
        God sent Jesus so you could see yourself.\n\n

God already knows who He is—He doesn\’t need your praise to make Him feel like God. God doesn\’t need
        you to tell Him how great He is—He knew it before you ever thought of praising Him. God wants
        you to know who you are—who you were supposed to look like. He\’s after the real
        person buried under the cap of your sin. Your IQ doesn\’t measure who you are, God does.
        Your true IQ is spelled H-O-L-Y S-PI-R-I-T, because you have what God is. Christ is in you.
        That\’s who you are.\n\n

PRINCIPLES\n\n

All things have the same components and essence as their source. When God created human beings,
        He spoke to Himself. You will never know yourself by relating to the creation, only to the Creator.
        Your potential is much greater than what you are right now. Your potential is limited only by God,
        not others. God sees Christ in you.\n\n
    </string>


</resources>
